{
    "subject": "resource/Burnout_Dominator",
    "predicate": "ontology/series",
    "object": "resource/Burnout_(series)",
    "human_readable": "Burnout Dominator is part of the Burnout series.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9742582440376282,
            "question": "What series is Burnout Dominator part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8895201086997986,
            "question": "Is Burnout Dominator considered a popular game within its series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.83580082654953,
            "question": "Is Burnout Dominator a standalone game or part of a larger franchise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7921876907348633,
            "question": "Who developed Burnout Dominator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.749789834022522,
            "question": "Can you name other games in the Burnout series besides Burnout Dominator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7072953581809998,
            "question": "Which gaming platforms did Burnout Dominator support?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6899873614311218,
            "question": "When was Burnout Dominator released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6595789790153503,
            "question": "What type of video game is Burnout Dominator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6049462556838989,
            "question": "What are some popular features of the Burnout series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4761173129081726,
            "question": "What are some common themes or gameplay mechanics in the Burnout series?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Burnout Dominator is part of the Burnout series.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3526_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular features of the Burnout series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3526_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of video game is Burnout Dominator?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3526_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Burnout Dominator released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3526_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3526_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the game Burnout Dominator, including its release dates, gameplay features, and system platforms. However, none of the documents explicitly state that it is part of the Burnout series. Nevertheless, every document assumes or describes the game as a part of the Burnout series, either by mentioning \"the legendary Burnout series\", \"Burnout game in the series\", \"installment of the Burnout series\", etc. Therefore, even though not directly stated, the information supports the triple that Burnout Dominator is part of the Burnout series."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that based on the provided context information, it is confirmed that \"Burnout Dominator is part of the Burnout series.\" The documents mention this game as an installment within the Burnout series multiple times."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}